no this is the wrong
remote what must I do what do you want
from me look lady this is the wrong
remote and this is the right remote okay
and you got to get the right remote I
have to find out I may or may not have
herpes to get this remote can I speak to
your manager please oh I am the manager
ala do billing installation programming
and I compose the unhold music you
compose this music oh no no this is the
waiting room music I compose that
too I'm actually the only person who
works here
yikes okay what are my options so you
can either mail in a check for $1,000 or
come in person and pay $5 you're only
the fifth person ever to come in
here I can pay in quarters right oh
actually no our system's down and we
only take nickels
sorry oh and you know what I hate your
music so do I and three and two and
[Music]
one